18 at least there is about
по 18 хоть есть о
super 21 years old let's talk about how do you feel
супер 21 года поговорим вот как вы
took ukraine
относитесь принял украине
for russia how do you feel about you don't
за россия как вы относитесь вы не
[music]
[музыка]
come out to joke and the gift of the basement I'm sitting here
выйти пошутить и дар подвале сижу тут
killing people and you're joking yes
людей убивает а вы шутите да
sorry
извините 1 как бы начал вселенский
I won’t put
я не буду наносить
on a shorter crest yes until before on this yes
на короче хохол да пока до на это да
shine whom I show the Turk attack
свети кого я показываю тюрк атака
turned out
получилась
jumped off and then I jump off bargain
спрыгнул и дальше спрыгну торгуешься
beshira scooter over the feeling in la cala de
бешира скутера над ощущению в la cala de
sen skilki showed the attack of the heart rich
sen скильки показал атаку сердце богатым
national multinational russia
национальная многонациональная россия
so sit kostya kostya russian girl so
так сидите костя костя россияночка так
create khk jumps  wreaths there it’s there a
создайте кхк скачет венках там оно там
friend was given out epicanthus and this is the currency for the
друга выданы эпикантус и это валюту на
manul of one race and the
манула одной расы и
lanterns on the valley you will give us for the Lansky
фонари на валью дашь нам за ланских
u-haul tattoo pancake with noisy in the lips of the robot
u-haul тату блин с шумны в губах робота
and we really will be given a drawstring from the
и нас правде кулиску из выдадут
wall handkerchief for discounts, you can easily
подручнике стен на скидки можно легко
first there mass on and
перво там масса на и
such  the girls themselves will be illustrations
такие сами девчата будут иллюстрациями
or construction legs of Petrovich, so you
или строительных петрович ногах так тебе
before in the materials the niche was a handyman, then
до в материалах ниша была подручнике то
on the 20th tailoring chair, then how can you be
на 20 пошива стуле то как можно быть
t  such an idiot in the
таким идиотом в
street the age of technology so so so in the
стрите эпоху технологий так так так в
taiga access tourism jal information that I
тайге доступ туризм jal информации того
sharpen once a year on so action
точу раза в год на так экшеном
english tajir alla information this is not
английских таджир алла информации это не
bowls filled with barking but these are people from all
миски заполнится лай но это люди из всех
information magazine choose find food and
журнал информации выбирают найду пищей и
fill moved away when I remove the jealous
заполняется отошли когда я сниму ревную
socket  that's
розетку вот
who's onion vinci secret coulter so
кто там луковиц винчи тайну коултер так
brush
кисть
gopnik so vindelitzia keys there vidosiki
гопник так винделиции keys там видосики
about about how there like lads etc.  and here is
про о как там типа братва и т.д. и вот
almost the published socks of
почти тк опубликованных носки intent у
Aliyev’s intent with his creaturely fill in his price for the
алиева него тварным заполните его цена
bracket and you we heal with the owl and the nightingale
скобе и вы мы совьем и соловьем исцелять
and donate here and there and
и жертвуют тут что там и они сижу меня
they sit me well
хорошо я не сижу в подвале тут а ты
hide my city 2 meters
аникеева hide my city 2 метров харьков
kharkiv skilki night of the Second World War
скильки ночь вов
at the metropolitan stations and in the rear there is a
на станциях митрополита и в тыл таится
language from such an hour you well, I’ll tell you
язык из такая часа ты ну я же расскажу
let the character interval and the pipe
пусть нам персонаж интервал а труба
will do it seriously deal with
будет does it серьезно заниматься
denazification Jesus and there even
денацификации иисусе и там уж пусть и
girls like that but Bachila Malaga you are
девчат таких но бачила малаги вы
Nazi  the mida here all that live in not
нацистким мида тут вся та живут в не
talking about us about our nation, ours
говорить про нас про нашу нацию нашу
kept it, and so
держал так вот
the grass also shows this retinue glory to
также трава показывают это свиту слава
ukraine
украине